MINJUNG KIM

■ minjung.kim@vision.snu.ac.kr | 🎓 Google scholar | 🖬 LinkedIn | 🗘 GitHub | 🗥 minnjung.github.io

♀ 317, Bldg 138, 1 Gwanak-ro, Gwanak-gu, Seoul, Korea

RESEARCH INTERESTS

My research focuses on **Visual Localization** and **3D Dense Captioning** for enhanced 3D scene understanding, with particular interest in: (i) understanding complex scenes from images and point clouds, (ii) effectively handling multi-modalities, and (iii) achieving a comprehensive understanding of 3D scenes through natural language.

EDUCATION

Seoul National University

Integrated M.S./Ph.D. Student in Computer Science and Engineering; (GPA: 4.03/4.3)

Vision and Learning lab, advised by Prof. Gunhee Kim.

Seoul, Korea

Mar. 2018 – Current

Sogang University

B.S. in Computer Science and Engineering; (GPA: 3.58/4.3), Magna Cum Laude

Mar. 2014 – Feb. 2018

Advised by Prof. Hyukjun Lee.

PUBLICATIONS

Bi-directional Contextual Attention for 3D Dense Captioning Minjung Kim, Hyung Suk Lim, Soonyoung Lee, Bumsoo Kim*, Gunhee Kim*	ECCV 2024 Oral presentation
Rethinking the Role of Queries in 3D Dense Captioning Minjung Kim, Gunhee Kim	KCC 2024
See It All: Contextualized Late Aggregation for 3D Dense Captioning Minjung Kim, Hyung Suk Lim, Seung Hwan Kim, Soonyoung Lee, Bumsoo Kim*, Gunhee Kim*	ACL 2024 Findings
EP2P-Loc: End-to-End 3D Point to 2D Pixel Localization for Large-Scale Visual Localization Minjung Kim, Junseo Koo, Gunhee Kim	ICCV 2023
Indoor/Outdoor Transition Recognition Based on Door Detection Seohyun Jeon, Minjung Kim, Seunghwan Park, Jaeyoung Lee	UR 2022
Drop-Bottleneck: Learning Discrete Compressed Representation for Noise-Robust Exploration Jaekyeom Kim, Minjung Kim, Dongyeon Woo, Gunhee Kim	ICLR 2021
Logo Detection and Recognition Algorithm using YOLO-v3 Model Minjung Kim, Sungen Kim, Gunhee Kim	CICS 2020
Memorization Precedes Generation: Learning Unsupervised GANs with Memory Networks Youngjin Kim, Minjung Kim, Gunhee Kim	ICLR 2018
Machine Learning for Determining Duplicate Question Minjung Kim, Yeongjoon Park, Hyungsuk Lim, Jihoon Yang	KSC 2017
Sketch based Face Image Generation with Text Mapping Minjung Kim, Hyungsuk Lim, Yeongjoon Park, Yeseul Joo, MyoungWan Koo	KSC 2017

DeepGuider | GitHub Apr. 2019 – May. 2023

• The DeepGuider Project is a national government-funded research project focused on developing a navigation guidance system that enables robots to navigate urban environments without the need for pre-mapping.

• I contributed by identifying clues to help locate autonomous robots, detecting and recognizing points of interest (POIs) in scene images, including text, landmarks, and doors for indoor-outdoor transitions, while also developing robust training methods to adapt to environmental changes.

PRIDE: 3D Place Recognition In Dynamic Environment | GitHub

Mar. 2022 - Apr. 2023

- This work proposes a new dataset called PRIDE, which includes dynamic objects such as cars and pedestrians, for 3D place recognition in dynamic environments that are more realistic and challenging than current benchmarks.
- The proposed PRIDE-Net architecture with a new loss function focuses on extracting discriminative global descriptors and capturing global context using spatial information, while being robust to dynamic environments.
- Experiments on the PRIDE dataset and existing benchmarks show that our proposed method outperforms previous methods and that each proposed module effectively improves performance.
- The code will be released after acceptance.

FCAT: Fully Convolutional Network with Self-Attention | GitHub

Dec. 2020 - Feb. 2022

- We construct a novel network named FCAT (Fully Convolutional network with a self-ATtention unit) that can generate a discriminative and context-aware global descriptor for place recognition from the 3D point cloud.
- It features with a novel sparse fully convolutional network architecture with sparse tensors for extracting informative local geometric features computed in a single pass. It also involves a self-attention module for 3D point cloud to encode local context information between local descriptors.

Bayesian Deep Learning course | *Lecture*

Feb. 2018 - Jul. 2018

- To understand deep learning papers, we explain the basic concepts of probability and Bayesian, and introduce papers related to Bayesian neural networks.
- This lecture can be taken through *edwith* of Naver Connect.

Sketch based Face Image Generation with Text Mapping | GitHub

Sep. 2017 - Feb. 2018

- A typical sketch might have been uncomfortable when a person or program was used to map a person's features in detail. This process is limited not only because it is very complex and requires technicians, but also because it creates a feeling of incompatibility with real people.
- This program, named Metamon, makes a picture of a person's face by entering the image of the border sketch of the person's face and the text information that shows the characteristics of the face.

Arduino & Raspberry Pi & Internet of Things (IoT) Tutorial | Project page

Dec. 2016 - Mar. 2017

- I create tutorial pages with Youtube videos and code for beginners in Arduino kit and Raspberry Pi development.
- I also introduce the concept of the Internet of Things (IoT) and work on a mini-project using *ThingSpeak*™.

Sogang Navigation and Introduction (SNI) | Github

Mar. 2015 - Jul. 2015

- We develop a navigation system that introduces the internal facilities of each building and displays the shortest route and time from building to building using the Floyd-Washall algorithm.
- To build data for the development, we measured the time taken by walking directly on each path.

EXPERIENCES

Vision and Multimodal Lab LG AI Research Research Intern Jun. 2023 - May. 2024 **KDB-SNU AI course** Seoul National University Teaching Assistant Apr. 2023 2022-3 SK hynix ML Engineer course Seoul National University Nov. 2022 - Dec. 2022 Teaching Assistant **KDB-SNU AI course** Seoul National University Apr. 2022 - May. 2022 Teaching Assistant LG AI core human resource training course Seoul National University Teaching Assistant Feb. 2022 loT · Artificial Intelligence · Big Data (IAB) course Seoul National University Sep. 2018 - Jun. 2019 Teaching Assistant **Bayesian Deep Learning course Naver Connect Publisher** Feb. 2018 - Jul. 2018 Vision and Learning Laboratory Seoul National University Jul. 2017 - Feb. 2018 Research Intern **Biointelligence Laboratory** Seoul National University Research Intern Sep. 2016 - Feb. 2017 Arduino & Raspberry Pi Kit Developer MakeWith (Startup) Dec. 2016 - Jan. 2017 Development Intern AWARDS & SCHOLARSHIPS YoulChon AI Star YoulChon Foundation (Nongshim Group) Fellowship Sep. 2024

Signal Processing section; Silver prize

Animal Datathon Korea Animal Tech Korea Predicting joint coordinates of a cow for pose estimation; **2nd place** Jul. 2021

Samsung Humantech Paper Award Samsung Electronics

KSC 2017 Paper Award Korean Institute of Information Scientists and Engineers

Feb. 2021

The undergraduate/junior thesis contest award Feb. 2018

Magna Cum Laude Honor Sogang University Feb. 2018 Academic Honors

Academic Excellence Scholarship Sogang University Jul. 2017 - Feb. 2018 Academic Honors

Windows 10 IoT Core & Microsoft Azure for Microsoft IoT Solution Competition Microsoft Implementing Internet of Things (IoT) projects with Windows 10 IoT Core and Microsoft Azure; 10th place Apr. 2017

Programming: Python, C, C++

Frameworks: Pytorch, TensorFlow/Keras **Tools:** Git, VSCode, Vim, Docker, Slurm

Others: Arduino, Rapsberry Pi

PROFESSIONAL ACTIVITES

Reviewer of International Conferences

- European Conference on Computer Vision (ECCV) 2024
- IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision (ICCV) 2023
- IEEE/CVF Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR) 2023
- Asian Conference on Computer Vision (ACCV) 2022
- International Conference on Learning Representations (ICLR) 2022, 2023
- Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS) 2021, 2022, 2023, 2024

Reviewer of International Journals

• International Journal of Computer Vision (IJCV) 2024

Technical Coaching

• 2022-3 SK hynix ML Engineer Technical Coaching